
Speaker 1  (00:04)
I think the ones that you know are pretty obvious to I wouldn't necessarily say exclude. But I don't know, probably wouldn't be recommended as a nom. Manufacturing organization pretty obvious not enough information found, you know, just more an indication that there's not a big online presence. 

Speaker 1  (00:27)
You're seeing me like AI script. The Web it wasn't able to find enough information to do classify it. Those will be ones that like childhood off my net already revie. 

Speaker 1  (00:36)
I think part of the analysis is digging in saying based on this Q Al data for the last 2 years. Which type function would you recommend looking at conversion rates? Looking at It's like total quadrant. 

Speaker 1  (00:51)
Yeah, there's a few that we look at that. I can't arrest off. We got a 50% conversion rate. 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
But we had 10 of them The realistically we have 10 like there's not really too much. We can do there. It's a pretty pretty small niche that we can't really get a lot of value out of it's almost a balanced act. 

Speaker 1  (01:17)
Hi. I'm made for a candy. 

Speaker 2  (01:22)
I'm so in part that can come with that. This doesn't make it come from within a result on the number of companies. And the conversion rate, what about this? 

Speaker 2  (01:35)
This means 6 credit cards is just manufacturing domain. 

Speaker 1  (01:44)
Yeah, this is, yeah, this is what they I thought they produced. And there are yeah, I think 6070 different groupings, which is pretty granular. I guess is something where you could put in a year. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
The 70 different categories accuse AI your own knowledge system together and enlarge your bucket. I'm also looking at the industry of the target industry. We have another higher level segment, CDC. 

Speaker 1  (02:11)
Of this data, the app, there's a few ways to slice it. I wanted to give you this granular data. Maybe it's a little too granular. 

Speaker 1  (02:20)
Maybe you want to roll it out. Just make sure you haveyou've statistical significance. Now please truly base your analysis on. 

Speaker 1  (02:32)
I don't know if that answers us question. 

Speaker 2  (02:35)
So our company's these are not categories that companies find themselves in unique for they may be in more than one category. 

Speaker 1  (02:45)
Oh, yes, but these are We kind of give it AI. The The ability or detail is to take one. Whichever And it has the largest presence, for example, they may do physical, manufacturing and I used disposables, but yeah, we haven't cost 56 to 1. 

Speaker 1  (03:10)
Is whichever water is coming up tomorrow? If you whoever want to rain has the biggest present. 

Speaker 3  (03:18)
Hello, yeah, thank you guys so much. I have a gold plastic. I'm killing alphabet, and he's talking about forecas. 

Speaker 3  (03:29)
We'll have which is aw. 5 sort of sector that we would be targeting for 

Speaker 1  (03:35)
My big example is deliverable. Costs are possible. 

Speaker 3  (03:39)
Operations, managers and Electrical directors and new help companies. While that means 4 minutes ago. 

Speaker 1  (03:48)
I know there's a lot of ways to supply. 

Speaker 3  (03:50)
9 which 1 we're actually going to go to Targeting was one. Mobile, but as far as life. 

Speaker 1  (03:59)
When you guys are 

Speaker 3  (04:01)
Looking at targeting a specific sector I mean, terminally, how much are you taking away from the account? The profitability of the contract level being signed. And if we have any access to One, so the averages would be for the expected revenue to bring in. 

Speaker 3  (04:21)
Or is that something that you can pay? And kind of interboating ourselves Deciding on which one we With the impact, depending on what we're doing, converting rates Vs the actual pro 

Speaker 1  (04:35)
We're expecting. Hell yeah, yeah, I think that's a good a good question of having to think about Now, specifically with, like the target or not. The company size came or which feel I use in this one. 

Speaker 1  (04:48)
So I believe I have like a large medium and small classification. The size of the company so giving that larger company like it's probably gonna be a harder sell, but it's gonna bring in more revenue. If you get more profitable, a smaller tier customer, you know, it may be a better fit for mass control. 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
But maybe it's not a profitable. Maybe it's not as large of an a CDI think for this analysis, let's leave out like potential profitability and look at purely conversion rates like that's the thing to kind of optimize to So want to see if when to get and how often you're gonna win them? Do you think about we're gonna give this to an FDR we're gonna give this Definitely worked for say a 100 contacts in a day. 

Speaker 1  (05:34)
Which contact do they go after and which account to get the largest number of wins in a in a year and a quarter they get caught in the number of opportunities they create the number of winds. They get not necessarily like how big the company is. I would optimize for it. 

Speaker 1  (05:52)
How can we get the most amount of wind rather than potential profitability? Yeah, so we'll focus more on the apple conversion. Professional profitability, if we did, we could take averages to say, like, well, we think the probability is. 

Speaker 1  (06:10)
But And why they're looking to buy. And how many licenses they want to purchase? How hard debt hard to sell? 

Speaker 2  (06:21)
Hi, thank you. Thank you. I think what's in this case. 

Speaker 4  (06:28)
Okay, thank you. I had 2 questions. One question is along those same lines. 

Speaker 4  (06:33)
When we talk about We were handing issues over to the gold science Is there any capacity piece tonight? I'm then, linked from remote work to manhandle. Unlimited volume, it's just more of a Titan. 

Speaker 1  (06:52)
Yeah, we have. You know, a limited number of SD R is within a given day. They have a certain number of calls and emails. 

Speaker 1  (07:00)
They can send you haveyou've a constraint there. I think the way that I would think about it is. Can you come up with a way to order these? 

Speaker 1  (07:08)
So, you know, I'll say that I'm an FDR and I have a call drop. I, have 15 minutes plus the next desk I doubt I should go after and you know, whether you assume we can do a 100 and day or a 1000A day coming up a way to rank these. And then whenever they do have time at 8, give the next step. 

Speaker 1  (07:27)
Available one or as a rule of thumb go after these types of companies or these types of titles or these people have Just when you've heard and what is the next best thing that can they can go after? 

Speaker 4  (07:41)
I got your priority center. Then, please call you, please. 

Speaker 1  (07:44)
Yeah, and we we have AI. Can internally we have like an Every account is ranked from 0 to 100. We'll say you haveyou've extra time as well. 

Speaker 1  (07:57)
Let's put all my accounts. This is a 99. Let's go for that one. 

Speaker 1  (08:02)
And we also have kind of a range of contacts. So within the ict V would be accounts. I should be going after these are the types of accounts. 

Speaker 1  (08:10)
I should be reaching out to based on that that contact covering your score. I'm safe, okay, that's what they 

Speaker 4  (08:26)
Of your interest in master control existing customer labs. If you knew at all kind of the ratio of how many of them are in both product lines Vs just A2S or just AS 

Speaker 1  (08:40)
Yeah, I think right now, we're about 80% 80 60 70% yearly qx. Probably 10%, 15% combo. And then another 10 to 15. 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
Understand just MXI want me to call out. Could you call that up? I assume for this sake of this analysis that everything you're looking at is purely prospect, but it didn't give you any of our some of our customer funnel. 

Speaker 1  (09:07)
Or potential pro style system assume these are all net new prospect accounts. We don't really have to complicate it with thinking about customers or which customers have one product rather than the other which assume these are all none of them have any mass control products right now in their they're all product. 

Speaker 4  (09:33)
Okay for the deliverable skills to try it or the focus of this is I'm a mass, not to identify you. 

Speaker 1  (09:42)
Yeah, that's kind of where we want to focus for the most part I was, I would wait to hear or promote you on MX. That wasn't hurt today. Yeah, this is somewhere where regardless of whether it's M. 

Speaker 1  (09:54)
You can focus, and here's ones that are purely Q. X. It is purely M. 

Speaker 1  (10:00)
X. 5 4 26 just focused primarily on examining index 

Speaker 2  (10:13)
I'm calling our next question. 

Speaker 1  (10:16)
Yeah, I can hear you okay. So I noticed that 

Speaker 5  (10:21)
I'm APAC, and we have a lower con. I'm connected. And I also noticed that you have I know what particular kind of thing, but So okay, I'm wondering, like, how do you move? 

Speaker 5  (10:40)
A time whether it's important. Already wanted priority 3 lessons, embarrassed and a possibil. And also, roughly how about 4 costume documents? 

Speaker 5  (10:51)
Hi, where I will please 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
Yeah, the P1 versus P2 classification is based purely on the type of content being downloaded to our website and you know right away, click a contact using tent behind that if I want to talk to your reps that would be AP1 contact us or contact you contact us. I believe we call it if you just came and like we have some materials pretty general, and just consider it kind of pop a funnel where you're more just trying to understand what mass control does what solutions we have more like doing your own research. 

Speaker 1  (11:33)
That's more of like a pq classification, where like, if you want to know about mass control, but you're probably not ready to buy right now. You can have early phase looking to understand what U s's are the benefits they have when mass control does. And then to your point about a pack. 

Speaker 1  (11:54)
In general, like across the company, we just kind of perform lower there. Different regulatory challenges. They face our product is developed. 

Speaker 1  (12:05)
Primarily, for like the US avia regulation. Well, there isn't as strong of a regul. We're bringing meat out there. 

Speaker 1  (12:14)
Overall, we needed to kind of perform before we were out there. But we did it. I'll accompany the regulations that they run into. 

Speaker 1  (12:30)
Any other any other questions? 

Speaker 2  (12:34)
I think Andrew has a successful stop for driving. I remember you mentioned that NASA controls considered a midget company to email once responsible cyber and FDA. Can you give us your perspective? 

Speaker 2  (12:49)
What the criteria of typically used to decide comp And what makes NASA control fall into the list? 

Speaker 1  (12:58)
You have our cheering system is based on the number employees. I believe it's anywhere from a 100 employees. Unless is a small tier company, and then about a 100 to excuse a 1000 or 2000 of that range is mid here and then over that would be That's the high tier, the large large companies, and I was more saying that primarily we have a higher wind rate, a more customers that are in that that is your range. 

Speaker 1  (13:32)
I'll tell you. I've really a large company. They're coming up with. 

Speaker 1  (13:35)
This is due. I can't do their own you on that develop it in-house. If there are smaller tiers, they usually don't have a budget to pay for this year product. 

Speaker 1  (13:46)
Like ours, well, I'm just kind of where we've we've seen, we do pretty well. 

Speaker 2  (13:56)
I'm good anybody else. Thanks to me. 

Speaker 1  (14:00)
Thank you of any attacks. 

Speaker 2  (14:08)
Thank you so much for 

Speaker 6  (14:10)
And I don't know if you can like meet them. 

Speaker 4  (14:14)
Are you with them? 

Speaker 1  (14:15)
Yes, I'll say that's a big question. I don't think you don't know too many of them office. My heads. 

Speaker 1  (14:20)
I don't know what you no as 5. 

Speaker 7  (14:24)
The actual regulations are not 

Speaker 1  (14:25)
Not entirely. 

Speaker 7  (14:27)
Go ahead and think about it. 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
Anyone who should be audited? 

Speaker 7  (14:30)
5 BFD A. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
For anything? 

Speaker 7  (14:33)
This will be indeed my go in in August 14. We helped to. You get everything in place. 

Speaker 1  (14:40)
If you ready for those sorts of things 

Speaker 7  (14:42)
Type of regulation, so that's a good Kind of all I can do about it. I don't know being on the internal team that keeps us. I know your problem. 

Speaker 7  (14:50)
So the actual light, what I think regulates the suspicious 

Speaker 2  (14:57)
You're 

Speaker 6  (14:58)
Yeah, no, if you look more like children, what type of companies you know, are more likely to get a drug source? So mcs DA 

Speaker 7  (15:07)
Yeah, yeah, so anyone anyone is producing anything. Medical would be someone who would need some pretty strict regulation. Just manufacturing in general, this is a lot of relations around I just pleasure to think from a factoring line. 

Speaker 7  (15:21)
So you add it to this Medical related any manufacturer, I guess. 

Speaker 1  (15:27)
Call in contacts with people. 

Speaker 3  (15:29)
But heavily on the medical side 

Speaker 1  (15:34)
The government makes sure that give our dotting there. I would pro I see the distance go in their own body, like it's a lot tricky regulation then creating, like a computer part of it and maybe it doesn't work. Just on it. 

Speaker 1  (15:49)
You don't come up with you know. 

Speaker 4  (15:52)
I could comment. I've worked 17 years for medical device. At NR in our quality management system, there's a lot of things that like regulations and certifying that they can't Like our free sell upgrade 2. 

Speaker 4  (16:07)
So they they won't have a paper. And then also in the quality. You have to have ways of laboring any kind of affordable event, always for the FDA or like, are there NB staff and B fly regul? 

Speaker 4  (16:22)
I'd love to sell in for Europe. A lot of it is just controlling the documents. The devices 3 records have maintained for each product that you're putting out into the sales. 

Speaker 4  (16:32)
So if they're That you can go and snap down. Like 230 products that were all built at the same time with this inequality component. And then all the signatures that bulb will stop. 

Speaker 1  (16:49)
Great, thanks. Was that. Thank you really helpful. 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
Thank you, so thank you. 

Speaker 8  (16:55)
You have just a chip in, just a chip. In. My understanding is that GMP right. 

Speaker 7  (17:01)
Manufacturing practic. 

Speaker 8  (17:03)
We kind of just stood on umbrella park, so I think if they want to see what it is specifically required on the GMP. I'm guessing that that side is The application process again, that's happened. We can just use T and P. 

Speaker 8  (17:16)
Isaac casual name will one of the requirements this year. Specific regulations? No one's always either against you. 

Speaker 8  (17:23)
The very 66. I think a lot probably flies over the general precious questions of Specifically, based on particular areas. 

Speaker 2  (17:38)
Yeah, let's play ideas. In fact, yes, doing that kind of research should definitely address your to your project. I will return Matt question. 

Speaker 3  (17:51)
Yes, this is a question about the missing data. And the way to handle that is cost. 

Speaker 2  (18:00)
And you guys are 

Speaker 3  (18:02)
When this sort of analysis is already happen. Internally, is there A 

Speaker 2  (18:08)
Preferred, a method. 

Speaker 3  (18:10)
Dealing with information data, I'll be free at a certain It's become well to contact process is entitled. Might be worth dropping, just because someone's 30% of the information we're seeing, but for those ones that range from Neil, under 1%. 2 and a 1 percent 

Speaker 2  (18:30)
I am usually called, okay from averages 0 specificity. 

Speaker 3  (18:36)
You kind of fill in the gas for that data. And a specific way that you're expecting it done to this project. 

Speaker 1  (18:44)
Yeah, that's a good question. With gold, I think, is it is very column specific but it is titled they don't have the title. If that doesn't necessarily mean they're not a quality person to reach out to you doesn't mean they're not gonna potentially buy a match control, I would think to have that will arrange since You know someone like that, you know, operation DP or a manufacturing DP now there are titles that I think you have a higher score than them, but also let's say there are probably titles that are worse than no information. 

Speaker 1  (19:20)
Like, I would almost fill it in with like a blank value, or you know, no information value. And when you're doing your analysis BDC. And does it actually rank at the bottom? 

Speaker 1  (19:30)
Does it rank kind of mid to your and give us the recommendation on what you would do with those types of contacts? If are they worth contacting have? We won any of it haven't had a title that might be might be feud. 

Speaker 1  (19:46)
I would assume a lot of the ones that we do connect with, and it wasn't a title. We probably built it in Hi, I would think that this could come up with pretty pretty low conversion rates, pretty low in the ring team that That's something that you could good luck into. And make the call on 

Speaker 3  (20:04)
Got this so freaked all in this. Comment off you all's discretion of how we want. Our 

Speaker 1  (20:09)
Your local tall values. Yeah, yeah, but I'll say I found your yeah, I'm trying to think of their at are any that I would ride away. Then, we're into, like hike. 

Speaker 1  (20:21)
Can I clean the data? I took out some things that would Confusing, you're just out of the snow for If that word's analyzing, I think I left everything in there that was And whether it's filled in or not, I think it's build anything and Analyzing guns. Well, I would get default to not excluding anything right away. 

Speaker 3  (20:50)
Tom Jim. 

Speaker 2  (20:58)
I will cost and distance 3 grates. Keeping coming, Mrs got him. 

Speaker 2  (21:18)
Well, the trouble of good time, if you're no more questions. Please call if you continue for after the race secure. 

Speaker 1  (21:32)
How about den on your address? This is a plan. I've given a little more time digging into it. 

Speaker 1  (21:38)
As we ask questions you're I've taken those biggest stabs out in. If you can figure it out or something got coming up and I'll reach out with that. 

Speaker 2  (21:47)
Exactly. So we'll be fit in keeping selecting not overwhelmed with winoff. Emails, you know, potentially repetitive, you haveyou've email. 

Speaker 2  (21:57)
And let us call up, you know, questions and check out. This call is Anthony pixton's view and ensure the sue you know, at a certain point. In this we'rewe are your you. 

Speaker 2  (22:13)
Haveyou've been 2 shifts? Roger's meeting to stand up meetings with individual teams, and so thank you, Mike pence, and you know, questions coming out of those individual teams, you could get people into their analysis. That we wouldn't share if you tired, you that was just a team of outset. 

Speaker 2  (22:40)
Call, yeah, but by basically 0, we are mistakenly. You know 3 or something like the next? Can I answer as soon as you're going to be listening and your security appointment from business 730 to EPA system modeling? 

Speaker 2  (23:04)
And then a good effort on the presentation. We can focus on different values and we are making a case for decisions that are your positive recommendations. You will come back together and think we're scheduled for middle E. 

Speaker 2  (23:30)
I missed April. And I'll be, I guess, just call in. Hey Mr. 

Speaker 2  (23:37)
Park sent you an evil today. I'll still figure that out soon and send out those invites and get a moment. And On both sides will be in patients, and you'll be at all. 

Speaker 2  (23:53)
We'll hopefully if you're walking there invites, I'll use anybody to make me get interested in listening to those. And there's absolutely done helping them. Please be welcome to all of Now in teams we're going to have that one5 minutes plus one2 + one2 plus questions. 

Speaker 2  (24:17)
So we shouldn't have enough time to go and zoom into the last few 

Speaker 1  (24:25)
Yeah, that's great. I'll try and get a simple detail from marketing that comes well and to be good for them. So I'll be there and take any information and give additional contacts. 

Speaker 1  (24:36)
If you needed. Hello, got our gotta wrangle, Josh up. You wanted. 

Speaker 1  (24:41)
You can make it to one meeting. 

Speaker 2  (24:44)
Call, then that would be great. Yeah. So businesses are for no more customs requests for tonight. 

Speaker 2  (24:52)
And this is we'll come see what is coming up here. We gotta keep it. This score won't be talking about specific problems. 

Speaker 2  (25:06)
Certain assignments and well, I'm here. Eric and jaywood, I can just point out that all presentations would be April 8th and April 16th. And we probably won't use all this time. 

Speaker 2  (25:23)
But I'll be, I'll be in touch with us. When exactly cancel and I'll send you an individual. Officer, hello, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (25:36)
Everybody, thanks for coming Ellison, Taylor and I'm We'll be in hacksmith. 

Speaker 1  (25:42)
Tehran, good luck. 

Speaker 3  (25:44)
Okay? And yesterday. 

Speaker 2  (32:08)
Xi jinp. 
